公共播报:大家请注意,
Public Announcement: Attention people;
有兴趣在多娜护士假释听证会上做证的人,请到办公室报告.
those interested in testifying at Nurse Downer's parole hearing should
祝大家一天顺利.
report to the office.Have a nice day.
卢克:好了,她来了.现在冲刺的时候到了.
Luke: All right, there she is.The time to strike is now.
本:没有什么东西从我鼻子流出来吧?
Ben: Nothing weird hanging out of my nose?
卢克 :跟平常一样.
Luke: Just the usual.
本:什么?那好吧!我不去了!
Ben: What?That's it!I'm not going!
卢克:就到那里去跟她说两句.
Luke: Just get over there and talk to her.
本:嘿,贝克.
Ben: Hi, Becka.
贝克:嘿,本.
Becka: Hi, Ben.
本:听着…
Ben: Listen...
剃刀:嘿!四眼!我让你跟贝克说话了吗?
Razor: Hey!Four eyes!Did I say that you could talk to Becka?
本:实际上,我叫本.
Ben: Actually, my name's Ben.
剃刀:闭嘴!知道吗,
Razor: Shut up!You know, I don't like your attitude.
我不喜欢你这态度.我讨厌你说话的样子.我甚至讨厌你的呼吸的摸样.
I don't like the way you talk.I don't even like the way you breath.
本:鼻音轻了?鼻音重了?还是从嘴里吐气多了?
Ben: Less nasal?More nasal?A little more through the mouth?
剃刀:事实上,你身上唯一让我喜欢的就是你的帽子.
Razor: In fact, the only thing I do like about you is your cap.
本:谢谢,我刚买的.
Ben: Thanks, I just got it.
剃刀:把它给我.
Razor: Give it to me.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
剃刀:快把它摘下来,放在我的手上.
Razor: Take it off your head,
我数三下.1!
and put it in my hand by the time I count to three.One!Two...Chicken.
2…小鸡!为什么不快点儿.
Why don't you cluck?
本:听着,剃刀,我知道你很历害,
Ben: Look, Razor, I know you're a tough guy,
可有些事我是不会去做的.啊,那么我们在这里谈什么呢?
but there are certain things I will not do.Uh, so what are we talking here?
谈罗德岛怪物,那可是有点…(咯咯叫)?还是泽西岛巨人,那可有点…(咯咯叫)?
Like,  Rhode Island red, which is kind of a...(clucking)?Like a Jersey giant, which is kind of ....(clucking)?
麦琪:克莉丝,我说过了,进浴室去.
Maggie: Chrissy, I told you to get in the bath.
克莉丝:我不想进.
Chrissy: I don't want to.
杰森:(清喉咙)
Jason: (clearing throat)
克莉丝:好吧,爸爸!随便你说什么!
Chrissy: Okay, daddy!Whatever you say!
麦琪:等一等,她这么不听我话,你就光清清喉咙?这算什么,是一种最简单的心理艺术,还是什么?
Maggie: Wait a minute.She ignores me totally, and you just clear your throat?What is this, some kind of psychological minimalist type of thing?
杰森:不,不,
Jason: No, no.Just kind of a, you know,
只是有一点,你知道,是鸡骨头卡在喉咙里了.
choking on a Chik-let kind of thing.
本:就这样!我已经下决心了,
Ben: That's it!I've made my decision, and you're not talking me out of it.
你们不必再劝我了.我要一支枪.
I want a gun.
杰森:(喘气)休想!
Jason: (gasping) Forget it!
本:好吧,你把我劝住了.
Ben: Okay, you talked me out of it.
第二个计划:我要去学空手道.
Here's plan B; I want to take karate lessons.
杰森:空手道.
Jason: Karate?
麦琪:为什么?
Maggie: Why?
本:你们还记得花27块钱买的新帽子吗?那个在学校里被叫作"剃刀"的家伙把它抢走了,
Ben: You guys remember my brand-new $27 cap?
就当着贝克和大家的面.
Well, this punk at school named Razor
made me give it to him in front of Becka and everybody
杰森:算了,本,你必须要对这种欺凌弱小的行为做斗争吗,为了…那顶27块钱买顶帽子?
Jason: Come on, Ben, you've had to deal with bullies before...$27 cap?
本:那小子特别厉害.他是学校里的霸王.
Ben: This kid is dangerous.He is certified USDA mean.
杰森:那么,我认为你应该把这件事报告副校长.
Jason: Well, I think you should report this to the vice-principal.
本:是吗?去年有个同学试过了.
Ben: Yeah?A kid tried that last year.
结果现在他隐名埋姓生活在内华达呢.
Now he's living in Nevada under an assumed name.
杰森:一定还有更好的解决办法.本,你为什么不直接去…
Jason: There's gotta be a better way to handle this, Ben.Why don't you just go...?
本:空手道怎么了?
Ben: What's so about karate?
它启发人的哲学思维,它的动作优雅,
I mean, it's philosophical, it's graceful,
还能教你如何用脚踹别人的头.
and it teaches you how to put your foot through somebody's brain.
麦琪:噢!本,你如果为这去学空手道,那就别想了.
Maggie: Oh!Ben, if that's why you want to learn karate, you can forget it.
本:好啊!
Ben: Fine!Then let me go look in my closet to see if I have anything
那让我看看衣橱里还有什么剃刀可以穿上身的.
else in Razor's size.
杰森:本!等一等,
Jason: Ben!Wait a minute, Ben.
本.麦琪,也许让他上几堂空手道课程并不是个坏主意.
Maggie, maybe it's not such a bad idea to let him take a few karate lessons.
麦琪:不行.
Maggie: No way.
杰森:你不懂这是怎么回事.
Jason: Well, you don't know what it's like.
你没尝过在学校里被人欺负的滋味.
You've never had somebody bully you around at school.
麦琪:实话跟你说吧,
Maggie: Well, as a matter of fact,
在整个大学一年级的时候,
Didi Ribozo tried to keep me from using the girl's bathroom the entire
迪迪·利伯佐试图不让我用女厕所.
junior year.
杰森:那你怎么办呢?
Jason: So what did you do?
麦琪:我在学校的时候不喝水.
Maggie: I gave up liquids during school hours.
杰森:看,你让步了.你不希望本也使用这种方式吧.
Jason: See, you gave in.That's not the way you want Ben to solve this.
麦琪:我明白,杰森.
Maggie: Well, I know that, Jason.
但我也不希望他用脚踹别人的脑袋.
But I also don't want him putting his foot through someone's brain.
杰森:现在,别人的脑袋在本的帽子里呢.
Jason: Well, right now, someone's brain is inside Ben's cap.
跟你一样,我也不喜欢暴力.
I don't like violence any more than you do,
可他如果知道任何保护自己,咱们俩感觉会好些.
but we're both gonna feel better if he knows how to protect himself.
麦琪:是啊,可我还是希望他能和那个孩子讲道理.
Maggie: Yeah, but I just wish there was some way he could reason with this boy.
杰森:麦琪,这是我的经验,
Jason: Maggie, it is my experience there are two kinds of people;
世界上有两种人:一种人可以跟他讲道理,另一种人就像剃刀这样的.
those you reason with, and those named Razor.
德怀特:迈克,我真的很感激,你能抽出时间来帮我买车.
Dwight: Mike, I really appreciate you taking the time to help me sell my car.
迈克:啊,我怎么能不帮你呢?
Mike: Oh, how could I not help?
而且,德怀特,你有可能娶开萝尔,
And Dwight, you could be the man that marries Carol, and takes her far,
把她带到很远很远的地方.我还得提前谢你呢.
far away.I'm just thanking you in advance.
买车人一:打扰了,我是来买车的.
Car buyer1: Excuse me.I'm her about the car.
迈克:哦,好的!老实告诉你,这车一出厂,模型就销毁了.
Mike: Oh, yes!I'm telling you, they broke the mold when they made this baby.
德怀特:哦,但愿这是真的.
Dwight: Oh, I sure hope so.
这车的毛病不少:发热管坏了,传送带老化了,
It's got a faulty heater hose, the fan belt's worn out,
下雨发动不起来,发动机老是嗡嗡嗡的响,
it doesn't start in the rain, the starter kinda goes ruhn-ruhn,
还有就是一打开收音机指示灯就灭了.
and when you turn the radio on the lights go off.
买车人一:再见!
Car buyer1: Good luck!
迈克:德怀特!你干什么啊?
Mike: Dwight!What are you doing?
德怀特:实话实说啊.
Dwight: Telling the truth.
迈克:这样能卖二手车吗?
Mike: To sell a used car?
德怀特:迈克,你不是在建议我撒谎,是吗?
Dwight: Mike, you aren't suggesting that I lie, are you?
迈克:不!我在命令你撒谎.
Mike: No!I'm ordering you to lie.
德怀特:迈克,我这辈子就撒过一次谎.
Dwight: Mike, I've only lied once in my whole life.
我没洗手,却告诉我妈饭前我洗过手了.
I told my mother that I'd washed my hands before dinner when I hadn't.
话音刚落,
The words were barely out of my mouth,
就有一大块不明飞行物从我家房顶上猛砸了下来.这就是征兆,
when a very large piece of Skylab came crashing down through our roof.
迈克.
It was an omen, Mike.
迈克:好吧,小鸡.
Mike: Okay, Chicken Little.Well, then we won't call it lying.
那么,我们不管这叫撒谎.我们只是在强调它的优点.
We'll just call it accentuating the positive.
你应该好好想一想这辆车有什么好处,而且对得起良心.
You know, try to think of the good things you can say about the car with a clear conscience.
德怀特:如果有人从后面撞了这辆车,
Dwight: If you get hit from behind,
它很有可能不会爆炸.
there's a pretty good chance it won't explode.
迈克:好!你看,这不难,对不对?
Mike: Great!You see, that's not so hard, is it?
德怀特:是的.
Dwight: No.
迈克:好了.
Mike: Okay.
德怀特:但我不撒谎.
Dwight: But I will not lie.
迈克:德怀特,我百分之一百一的赞成你.
Mike: Dwight, I'm with you 110 percent.
好了,咱们边修里程表边商量吧.
Okay, let's talk about it while we roll back the odometer.
麦琪:好了,本,我们必须到后面拿你的训练服了.
Maggie: Okay, Ben, we have to go in back to get your uniform.
本:哦,我就去.(梦境:本的拳头)
Ben: Oh, I'll be right there.[Dream sequence: The Five Fingers of Ben]
长毛大汉:嘿,你!
Villian leader: Hey, there, you!Blond boy!
黄毛小子!有人说,你在到处找我?
People say you are looking around to find me.
本:正确!我恨你恨得咬牙切齿.(集体起哄)
Ben: Correct!I hate you with great hatred.[gang noises]
长毛大汉:在你找的时候,
Villian leader: While you are looking for us,
我们已经把你们的人全杀光了.
we have decimated your little town.
长毛大汉:(笑)还打死了你的金鱼.
Villian: (laughing) And pistol-whipped your goldfish.
本:你会死的很难看.
Ben: Prepare for a very painful death.
长毛大汉:安静!我厌倦了这种絮絮叨叨的方式.
Villian leader: Silence!I am tired of this snappy patter.
动手吧,让我们干净利落地打一场吧.(叫喊声)
Let us fight and make snappy patter.
本:你打起来就像我的贝莎阿姨.
Ben: You fight like my aunt Bertha.
本:真可惜,你们只有5个.
Ben: It's a pity there are only five of you.
我本来希望能出出汗的.你们这群臭虫.
I was hoping to break a sweat.Swamp-dwelling insects.
长毛大汉:消灭他.(打斗声)
Villian leader: Destroy him.[fighting sounds]
本:(笑)
Ben: (laughing)
长毛大汉:黄毛小子!你还不赖,不过要想跟我打,你的手脚最好还是再灵活点儿.(打斗声)
Villian leader: Blond boy!You are not bad, but you must fight with greater dexterity
if you want to challenge me.[fighting sounds
长毛大汉:现在,我要打烂你的脸.(笑)
Villian leader: And now, I shall laugh in your face.(laughing)
本:没有人敢来打我的脸.现在是我打烂你的脸.(笑)现在,让你尝尝我的拳头.
Ben: Nobody laughs in my face.It is I who shall laugh in yours.(laughing)  And now, prepare yourself to taste my fist.
本:啊-呀!
Ben: Ai-yah!
麦琪:本,你没事吧?
Maggie: Ben, are you okay?
本:哦,是的.
Ben: Oh, yeah!
西蒙:再快点!再来一遍!1,2,3,4!
Sim: Faster!Again!One, two, three, four!
麦琪:呃,哦,打扰一下,打扰了.呃,西蒙师傅,西蒙师傅.
Maggie: Uh, uh, excuse me, excuse me, uh, Master Sim, Master Sim...
西蒙:告诉我,本.你看见过眼镜蛇和黄鼠狼打架吗?
Sim: Tell me, Ben.Have you ever seen a fight between cobra and mongoose?
本:呃,只看过迈克和爸爸因为房租的事打过…
Ben: Uh, just Mike and my dad when the rent's due.
西蒙:道理一样:攻击,发攻击.准备好!我们要加快节奏了.上!1,2,3…
Sim: Same principal; attack, counter-attack.Get ready!We're gonna go faster now.Go!One, two, three...
麦琪:不,不!西蒙师傅,求你了!你会伤着他的.
Maggie: No!No!Master Sim, please!You might hurt him.
本:啊,妈妈…
Ben: Aw, mom.
西蒙:本,休息一下.
Sim: Ben, take a break.
麦琪:对不起,西蒙师傅,但这太暴力了.
Maggie: I'm sorry, Master Sim, but this is all much too violent.
西蒙:西沃太太,空手道不是暴力.
Sim: Karate is not about violence, Mrs.Seaver.Karate is about control.
空手道是一种控制,
Control of yourself first,
首先要控制自己,然后控制试图伤害你的其他人.
and then control of someone who may be trying to hurt you.
本:看,妈妈,没人会受伤的.来啊,我来给你练几手…
Ben: Look, mom, no one's getting hurt.Come on, I'll show you.
麦琪:不,我经历过的唯一一次贴身战斗就是在抢购减价商品的时候.
Maggie: No, the only hand-to-hand combat I do is at the Macy's white sale.
本:不,妈妈,我只是让你看看,我怎么学会保护我自己.行吗,西蒙师傅?
Ben: No, mom.I'll just be showing you how I'm learning to defend myself.Is that all right Master Sim?
西蒙:是的.不过记住你妈妈没学过,
Sim: Yes, but remember your mother has had no lessons, so block her blows,
所以只格挡她的进攻,不能挥拳还击.
but don't counter-punch.
本:好的,妈妈.试一下,打我.
Ben: Okay, mom.Just try and punch me.
麦琪:啊!啊!
Maggie: Ah!Oh!
本:妈妈,是冲拳,不是拍打.来吧.
Ben: Mom, a punch, not a slap.Come on.
西蒙:步法不错,本.
Sim: Good footwork, Ben.
本:好,妈妈.这次要真的使劲才行.
Ben: Okay, mom.Now really let me have it this time.
麦琪:好的,本.准备好.
Maggie: Okay, Ben.If you're sure.
本:哎吆!
Ben: Ai-yah!
麦琪:(击打本)哦!哦!哦,我的天啊,本!
Maggie: (hitting Ben) Oh!Oh!Oh, my God!Oh, Ben!Are you all right, sweetheart?
你没事吧,宝贝?哦!哦,亲爱的!
Oh!Oh, honey!
迈克:嘿,本,我一直在思考你的问题.
Mike: Hey, you know, Ben, I've been thinking about your problem.
哦,我觉得你如果在以后三年的时间里坚持练空手道,
And I really think that if you keep up this karate,
而且真正地苦练,你会赢妈妈的.
and you study real hard for the next three years, you could take mom.
之后,还有谁?外婆?开萝尔?也许学校里一大半女孩.
After that, who knows; grandma, Carol, probably most of the girls at school.
本:妈妈打败了我.哥哥取笑我.
Ben: My mother clocks me.My brother makes fun of me.
我能有多么差啊?(梦境)
How much worse can this get?[Dream sequence: Enter The Wimp]
麦琪:嘿,你,小黄毛.我看你有些情绪低落,羞愧难当.
Maggie: Hey, you, little blond boy.I see you are depressed and humiliated.
本:哦,求你了妈妈,别取笑我了.
Ben: Oh, please, mom.Don't make fun of me.
麦琪:别傻了,小黄毛.
Maggie: Don't be silly, little blond boy.I would never do such a thing.
我永远不会取笑你的,除非有人跟我合伙,当然是家里人或是朋友.
Unless I had help of course, from family and friends.
Jason: You are so very weak.I have replaced your CD's with....Perry Como records
迈克:还涂抹了你的吉他.
Mike: And painted your guitar.
卢克:还偷了你的女朋友.
Luke: And stolen your girlfriends.
杰森:还给你的床铺上有小心脏和小花的床单.
Jason: And put new sheets on your bed decorated with tiny hearts and flowers.
本:来吧,你们.
Ben: Come on, you guys.
全家:(空手道声)
Entire family: (karate sounds)
麦琪:我打他都打烦了.让他学校里的朋友们来打吧.
Maggie: I grow weary of these attacks.Let his friends at school attack him.
本:不,求你了,妈妈,别让我去学校.
Ben: No, please, mom, don't make me go to school.
麦琪:别害怕,小黄毛.
Maggie: Have no fear, little blond boy.
我们会给你配一个可怕的保镖送你去学校.
We shall send you to school with a fearsome bodyguard.
克莉丝:哎-呀!我会保护你,
Chrissy: Ai-yah!I will protect you, little blond boy.
小黄毛.然后,我就嘲笑你了(笑)
And then I shall laugh in your face.(laughing)
麦琪:嘿,本,你没吃完早饭.
Maggie: Hey, Ben.You didn't finish your breakfast.
本:妈妈,我决定了,我不练空手道了.
Ben: Mom, I made my decision.I'm quitting karate.
麦琪:你想退出?
Maggie: You want to quit?
本:对.我想辍学,可这不合法;我要离家出走,可是我会饿死.
Ben: Yeah.I'd quit school but it's illegal.I'd quit the family but I'd starve.
我说,今天我能呆在家里吗?我觉得不太舒服.
Look, you mind if I stay home from school today?I'm not feeling so good.
麦琪:我觉得没什么.
Maggie: I guess it's all right.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
买车人二:哦,这辆看起来真不错.我买了!
Car buyer2: Well, it certainly looks fine.I'll take it!
德怀特:哦,这车有一两个问题,你也许应该…
Dwight: Oh, there are a couple of problems that you should probably....
迈克:呃,德怀特,呃,你是不是和我一样渴望吃上几个香喷喷的酒泡奶酪球?
Mike: Uh, say, Dwight, uh.Do you happen to have the same craving for some port wine cheese balls as I do?
德怀特:什么?是的,我想.我真想这个呢.
Dwight: Why, yes I do.I thought it was just me.
迈克:老兄,那你为什么不去买几个.这儿让我来成交.
Mike: Boy, I say, why don't you go whip us up some, and I'll, uh, close the deal.
德怀特:好的.
Dwight: Sure.
买车人二:他刚才说的那些问题是什么?
Car buyer2: What are these problems he's talking about?
迈克:哦,没问题,夫人.都怪德怀特.他觉得我们开的价太低了.
Mike: Oh, oh, nothing ma'am.That's just Dwight.He, he happens to think that we're not charging enough.
不过,不知从什么时候买车变的赚钱了?这只是互相帮忙,对吗?
But since when is selling a car about making money?It's about people helping people, right?
买车人二:(叹气)说到我的心窝里了.(喘气)看,下面那一团黑东西是什么?
Car buyer2: (sighing)  Isn't that sweet!(gasping)  Say, what's that black puddle under there?
迈克:哦,这完全正常.呃,
Mike: Oh, uh, th-that's perfectly normal.
这,就像人热了要出汗一样,呃,车正在冒湿气.
Uh, it's, well, just the same way that your body sweats, uh,
哦,嗯,这是健康的标志.
a car releases moisture.It's, uh, a sign of health.
买车人二:哦,我的朋友们说,我应该找个机械师好好检查一下.
Car buyer2: Well, my friends say I should have it checked by a mechanic,
可是,你看上去是那么忠厚老实,是不是我现在就把支票给你呢?
but you have such an honest face.Shall I make the check out to you?
迈克:可以.不!呃,可以.不,不!
Mike: Yes.No!Uh, yes.No, no!Ma'am, it's a rolling death trap.Quick!
夫人,这是个害人的陷阱.赶快!赶快离开这里,要不我又想把车卖给你了.
Get out of here before I sell it to you again.
德怀特:好,好,好,你说实话了.
Dwight: Well, well, well.You told the truth.
迈克:哦,我不是故意的.我只是说漏嘴了.
Mike: Well, I didn't mean to.It just slipped out.
德怀特:奶酪球?
Dwight: Cheese ball?
迈克:真是的!哦,对不起.
Mike: Dufus!Oh, sorry.
德怀特:迈克,我觉得你说的对.
Dwight: Well, Mike, I guess you're right.
说真话永远卖不了这辆车.
We'll never sell the car by telling the truth.
迈克:哦,是吗?我有主意了.德怀特,
Mike: Oh, yeah?Well, I got an idea.Dwight, you pop the hood.
打开车盖.我去拿工具,咱们把车修一修.
I'm gonna get my tools.You and I are gonna fix this car.
迈克:德怀特,那是行李箱.
Mike: Dwight, that's the trunk.
德怀特:哦,我的上帝!我把油加哪儿了?
Dwight: Oh, my God!Where have I been putting the oil?
杰森:好,就这样.我们就用你的方法对付本.
Jason: Okay.All right.We'll deal with Ben your way.
麦琪:相信我,杰森,会有用的.
Maggie: Trust me, Jason, it'll work.
杰森:上一次你这么说了以后,我们就不得不结婚了.
Jason: Last time you said that we had to get married.
麦琪:哦!他来了.
Maggie: Oh!He's coming.
杰森:嘿,本.你妈妈说你想放弃空手道课了.
Jason: Hey, Ben.Your mom says you want to give up karate lessons.
本:听我解释,爸爸,我努力了;我失败了;我的一生都完了.
Ben: Look, dad.I tried; I failed; my life is ruined.
杰森:没关系,你的眼睛会好的.
Jason: C'mon, that eye's gonna be fine.
可你没有任何理由不去接着上空手道课.
But there's no reason why you can't go right back to karate class.
麦琪:杰森,你在说什么呀?!
Maggie: Jason, what are you talking about?
跟他打的下一个人可能就不会像我这么爱他了.
The next person he fights might not love him like I do.
杰森:我只是不想让儿子因为受伤而放弃,麦琪.
Jason: Well, I don't want our son to give up just because he got hurt, Maggie.
麦琪:杰森,他不仅仅是受伤.他被摔出去,打瘪了,
Maggie: Jason, he wasn't just hurt.He was taken out, flattened, destroyed!
毁掉了!被他的妈妈!对不起,宝贝,你还疼吗?
By his mommy!I'm sorry, pookie, does it still hurt?
本:不,我现在就想平静地做个四眼儿笨蛋,他的屁股被自己的妈妈踢了.
Ben: No!I've made peace with being a four-eyed geek, whose butt was kicked by his mother.
杰森:本,我不希望你放弃,我要告诉你为什么.
Jason: Ben, I don't want you to quit, and I'm gonna tell you why.
本:哦,求你了,爸爸,别听演讲.
Ben: Oh, please, dad.No pep talks.
杰森:哦,别这样.你以前也失败过,本.每次失败后,
Jason: Oh, come on.I mean, you've been down before, Ben, and every time you've been down before,
你都会更加深刻的认识到"见鬼,我能做到",对吗?
you've reached down deeper for some of that "heck, I can do it" Seaver spirit, right?
本:我还以为你要给我演讲呢.
Ben: And I thought you were gonna give me a pep talk.
杰森:帽子的事怎么样了?
Jason: And what about the cap thing?
麦琪:哦,这很简单.从现在起,我们就给他穿朴素,简单的衣服,这样就不会有其他的孩子抢了.
Maggie: Oh, it's very simple.From now on, we dress him in plain, generic clothes that no other kid would be caught dead in.
本:等一下…
Ben: Wait a minute....
麦琪:杰森,让他放弃吧.
Maggie: Jason, let him quit.
杰森:哦,我们都把空手道课的学费交了.
Jason: Oh, we still gotta eat the cost of those karate lessons.
麦琪:克莉丝可以继续上.
Maggie: Well, Chrissy can take them.
杰森:啊.
Jason: Ah.
麦琪:亲爱的,我们要面对现实.很明显,
Maggie: Honey, we should just face it.
本不具备练武的天赋,他没有动力,或者说能力.
It's obvious that Ben doesn't have the talent, the drive, or the ability.
杰森:就是啊.他是个笨蛋.
Jason: God knows, he's a klutz.
本:好了,好了,我开始认识到"见鬼,我能做到"的含义了,
Ben: Okay, okay.I'm starting to feel that "heck, I can do it" Seaver spirit.
在就是西沃家的精神.妈妈,爸爸,我要继续学空手道.
Mom, dad, I'm going back to karate.
要知道,以前你们"一个白脸,
And you know, you guys used to be much better at this "good cop,
一个红脸"的表演要比这高明.
bad cop" thing.
麦琪:那么,是不是又信任我了?!
Maggie: So, would you glad trust me?
杰森:第二次.
Jason: Both times.
西蒙:上啊!哈!
Sim: Let's go!Huh!
西蒙:练习踢腿动作.
Sim: Recall your kicks.
麦琪:太棒了!好!
Maggie: That's great!Great!
买车人三:这辆车太旧了.性能怎么样?
Car Buyer3: She's kinda old.How's she holding up?
迈克:性能跟全新的一模一样,因为我已经,如果我说谎,让卫星掉下来砸着我,我不仅换了部件,还换了制动;
Mike: Just like brand new, because I have, and may a satellite strike me if
I'm lying, not only tuned it up, but I have changed the brakes
我检查了方向盘,修了油泵;我调换了所有的输油管,
I've checked the alignment, fixed the fuel pump,
而且调好了广播电台.
I have replaced all the hoses, and preset all the radio stations.
买车人三:听起来不错!你们收不收私人支票?
Car buyer3: Sounds great!Will you accept a personal check?
德怀特:不!
Dwight: No!
买车人三:给你看两种证件呢?
Car buyer3: Even with two forms of ID?
德怀特:不!
Dwight: No!
买车人三:好吧,我给你现金.
Car buyer3: All right, I'll offer you cash.
德怀特:不!我们不卖了.
Dwight: No!We're not selling.
迈克:德怀特!我们不干什么?
Mike: Dwight!We're not what?
德怀特:迈克,我想卖车只是因为它(车噪音),
Dwight: Mike, I only wanted to sell it cause it went (car noises),
可现在没有了!而且"嘟嘟嘟",
and now that's gone!It's going vroom-vroom!
我的心脏也"砰砰砰"地跳动有力.
And my heart's going thawagada-thawagada-thawagada.
迈克:德怀特,你这次能不能听我的.
Mike: Dwight, will you join me for a minute in this time zone?
德怀特:迈克,谢谢你.我又喜欢自己的车了.我们不卖了.
Dwight: Mike, thanks to you I love my car again.And we're not selling!
迈克:德怀特!你这个吃货,卷毛,中世纪的笨蛋!我为你这台破车付出了500块钱的劳动力.
Mike: Dwight!You cheese-eating, tangle-haired, medieval moron!I put over $500 of labor into this hunk of junk!
德怀特:谢谢你.
Dwight: Thank you.
卢克:哇!嘿,本!焕然一新啊.
Luke: Woo!Hey, Ben!Looking fresh.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
本:哦,是贝克.我终于准备好跟她说话了.
Ben: Well, it's Becka.Finally I'm ready to talk to her.
卢克:如果贝克出现了,剃刀也来了.
Luke: If Becka's around, so is Razor.
本:别担心.我知道该做什么.
Ben: Don't worry about it.I know what to do.
本:嘿,贝克.
Ben: Hi, Becka.
贝克:嘿,本.
Becka: Hi, Ben.
剃刀:嘿,笨蛋.
Razor: Hi, geek.
本:我叫本.
Ben: The name's Ben.
剃刀:哦,对了.你把它写在我的新帽子里了.
Razor: Oh, that's right.You had it written inside my new hat.
本:听着,我不想惹麻烦.
Ben: Look, I don't want any trouble.
剃刀:哦,是吗?
Razor: Oh, yeah?Well, you know what I want?
那好,知道我想干要什么吗?我想要你穿的这件新夹克.
I want that nice, new jacket you've got on.
本:好了,他站在我左边四分之三位.
Ben: Okay, he's facing me three-quarters to the left.
这样他没法对付我的进攻.我只要虚晃一下,进步向前,反踢他的肋骨,最后击打他的鼻子,把他打翻在地.
That leaves him wide open for a fake jab, step in, back-kick to the
ribs, and I can finish him off with a palm thrust to the nose
剃刀:你在看什么,笨蛋?
Razor: What are you staring at, geek?Am I gonna have to bust you one?
想让我动手吗?我说了现在给我.
I said give it to me now.
卢克:快叫护士,快,这家伙受伤了.
Luke: Somebody get the nurse, quick, this guys hurt.
剃刀:你在看什么,笨蛋?想让我动手吗?我说了现在给我.
Razor: What are you staring at, geek?Am I gonna have to bust you one?I said give it to me now.
卢克:不,我不会给你夹克的,或者其他什么,再也不了.
Luke: No.I'm not giving you this jacket, or anything else ever again.
剃刀:哇呜!成大人了?在说大话呢.好吧,笨蛋,过来.练两下,看看你都学了些什么.成硬汉了,哦!
Razor: Whoa!Big man, huh?Big words.All right, geek, c'mon, let's throw.Show me what you've got, tough guy, huh!
来吧,就在这练练,就现在!上来吧!
C'mon, let's go for it right here, right now!Go for it!
卢克:他一点没防备.这个纨绔子弟没见过这个.稳住,不要碰他,除非时机到了.
Luke: He's wide open.The dude will never see it coming.Control.Don't touch him unless you have to.
剃刀:来啊,笨蛋.上来啊.哦!哦!(咯咯叫)
Razor: C'mon, geek, let's go for it.Huh!Huh!(clucking)
本:我不想跟你打.
Ben: I'm not gonna fight you.
剃刀:听见了吗?他说不想跟我动手.
Razor: Did you hear that?He said he's not gonna fight me, huh.
嗯,我该做什么呢?
What am I supposed to do, huh?
站在他面前,把他当沙袋用吗?
Stand on his feet, and use him like a punching bag?
(笑)看看这个傻瓜,他僵住了.走吧,宝贝,咱们走吧.
(laughing) Look at the dude, he's frozen.Come on, babe, let's get out of here.
卢克:嘿,兄弟,你真令人吃惊.
Luke: Hey, man, you were amazing.
本:谢谢.我叉嗲就跟他动粗了.
Ben: Thanks.I came real close to getting ugly.
卢克:哦,说到动粗,你可以忘掉贝克的.她不值得你这样.
Luke: Well, speaking of ugly, you can forget about Becka.She's not worth it.
盖尔:对不起,本?
Gail: Excuse, me.Ben?
本:什么?
Ben: Yeah?
盖尔:我真的很喜欢你刚才的样子.
Gail: I really like the way you handled that creep.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
盖尔:午饭给你留个位置?
本:当然.我总是很饿.
00:22:14,900
Gail: Save you a seat at lunch? Ben: Sure.I'm always hungry.